// export const data = [
//     {
//       question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
//       option1: "Modem",
//       option2: "Router",
//       option3: "LAN Cable",
//       option4: "Pen Drive",
//       ans: 1,
//     },
//     {
//       question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
//       option1: "Asia",
//       option2: "Europe",
//       option3: "North America",
//       option4: "Africa",
//       ans: 4,
//     },
//     {
//       question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
//       option1: "Spam",
//       option2: "Fake",
//       option3: "Archived",
//       option4: "Bin",
//       ans: 1,
//     },
//     {
//       question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
//       option1: "Application Software",
//       option2: "Internet",
//       option3: "Operating System",
//       option4: "Mouse",
//       ans: 3,
//     },
//     {
//       question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
//       option1: "Index Page",
//       option2: "Homepage",
//       option3: "Sitemap",
//       option4: "Pen Drive",
//       ans: 2,
//     },
//   ];


export const data = [
  {
    question: "Who is the highest run-scorer in Test cricket for Pakistan?",
    option1: "Inzamam-ul-Haq",
    option2: "Younis Khan",
    option3: "Mohammad Yousuf",
    option4: "Misbah-ul-Haq",
    ans: 2, // Younis Khan
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani cricketer has taken the most Test wickets?",
    option1: "Wasim Akram",
    option2: "Waqar Younis",
    option3: "Shoaib Akhtar",
    option4: "Imran Khan",
    ans: 1, // Wasim Akram
  },
  {
    question: "In which year did Pakistan win their first T20 World Cup?",
    option1: "2007",
    option2: "2009",
    option3: "2011",
    option4: "2013",
    ans: 2, // 2009
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the captain of the Pakistan cricket team when they won the 1992 Cricket World Cup?",
    option1: "Wasim Akram",
    option2: "Inzamam-ul-Haq",
    option3: "Imran Khan",
    option4: "Javed Miandad",
    ans: 3, // Imran Khan
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani bowler is known for his 'doosra'?",
    option1: "Shoaib Akhtar",
    option2: "Saqlain Mushtaq",
    option3: "Saeed Ajmal",
    option4: "Shahid Afridi",
    ans: 2, // Saqlain Mushtaq
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for the highest individual score in ODI cricket for Pakistan?",
    option1: "Saeed Anwar",
    option2: "Fakhar Zaman",
    option3: "Imam-ul-Haq",
    option4: "Javed Miandad",
    ans: 2, // Fakhar Zaman
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani cricketer has the most centuries in Test cricket?",
    option1: "Younis Khan",
    option2: "Inzamam-ul-Haq",
    option3: "Mohammad Yousuf",
    option4: "Misbah-ul-Haq",
    ans: 1, // Younis Khan
  },
  {
    question: "In which year did Pakistan win their first ICC Champions Trophy?",
    option1: "2002",
    option2: "2004",
    option3: "2009",
    option4: "2017",
    ans: 4, // 2017
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the current captain of the Pakistan cricket team in T20Is?",
    option1: "Babar Azam",
    option2: "Sarfaraz Ahmed",
    option3: "Shoaib Malik",
    option4: "Shadab Khan",
    ans: 1, // Babar Azam
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani cricketer has the most sixes in ODI cricket?",
    option1: "Shahid Afridi",
    option2: "Inzamam-ul-Haq",
    option3: "Fakhar Zaman",
    option4: "Abdul Razzaq",
    ans: 1, // Shahid Afridi
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani cricketer is known as the 'Rawalpindi Express'?",
    option1: "Waqar Younis",
    option2: "Mohammad Sami",
    option3: "Shoaib Akhtar",
    option4: "Wasim Akram",
    ans: 3, // Shoaib Akhtar
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first Pakistani cricketer to score a triple century in Test cricket?",
    option1: "Hanif Mohammad",
    option2: "Javed Miandad",
    option3: "Younis Khan",
    option4: "Inzamam-ul-Haq",
    ans: 1, // Hanif Mohammad
  },
  {
    question: "In which year did Pakistan first play international Test cricket?",
    option1: "1947",
    option2: "1952",
    option3: "1956",
    option4: "1960",
    ans: 2, // 1952
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani cricketer is famous for hitting six sixes in an over during a T20 domestic match?",
    option1: "Imran Nazir",
    option2: "Shahid Afridi",
    option3: "Shoaib Malik",
    option4: "Iftekhar Ahmad",
    ans: 4, // Iftekhar Ahmad
  },
  {
    question: "Who captained Pakistan to victory in the 2009 ICC T20 World Cup?",
    option1: "Misbah-ul-Haq",
    option2: "Younis Khan",
    option3: "Shahid Afridi",
    option4: "Shoaib Malik",
    ans: 2, // Younis Khan
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani cricketer holds the record for the fastest century in ODI cricket?",
    option1: "Saeed Anwar",
    option2: "Inzamam-ul-Haq",
    option3: "Shahid Afridi",
    option4: "Babar Azam",
    ans: 3, // Shahid Afridi
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani bowler took a hat-trick in a World Cup match?",
    option1: "Shoaib Akhtar",
    option2: "Wasim Akram",
    option3: "Saqlain Mushtaq",
    option4: "Waqar Younis",
    ans: 3, // Saqlain Mushtaq
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first Pakistani cricketer to be inducted into the ICC Hall of Fame?",
    option1: "Wasim Akram",
    option2: "Imran Khan",
    option3: "Hanif Mohammad",
    option4: "Javed Miandad",
    ans: 1, // Wasim Akram
  },
  {
    question: "Which Pakistani wicketkeeper has the most dismissals in Test cricket?",
    option1: "Moin Khan",
    option2: "Wasim Bari",
    option3: "Sarfraz Ahmed",
    option4: "Rashid Latif",
    ans: 2, // Kamran Akmal
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the father of Pakistan Cricket Board?",
    option1: "Abdul Hafeez Kardar",
    option2: "Imran Khan",
    option3: "Hanif Mohammad",
    option4: "Javed Miandad",
    ans: 1, // Abdul Hafeez Kardar

  }
  // Add more questions to reach at least 20
];
